HANEEN AI-FAR

Front-End Developer

Mob: +971 552237661 Dubai | UAE hanin.alfar93@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To get a career opportunity which would help me to utilize my academic and vocational background to assist me to gain more experience, with allowing me to utilize my knowledge and skills, and enable me to make positive contribution.

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Web Developer Engineer

Feb 2021 - Present

Freelance

- A diligent, skilled Freelance Web Developer with 1+ year of experience building websites in small business, agency, education and in-house sectors. Ambitious and excited to work on new projects and other opportunities.
- Designing, coding websites for the different projects using CSS, SASS, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery.

Pre-Seles May 2018 - Dec 2020

Arab News Broadcast (ANB), Jordan

- Ability to work as a team, and to work under pressure.
- Problem solving skills.
- Effectively guide and work with a variety of individuals through the best possible
- solution.
- Developing professional relationships with clients and staff.
- Ability to communicate well in a professional setting (written and verbal)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) - Computer Engineering Sep 2011 - May 2018 University of Jordan, Jordan

- **Tutoring**: I have been explaining many subjects to my colleagues at the university.
- **Graduation Project**: Emotion Recognition based on Matlab language simulation, you can implement user registration, the number of emotions such as feelings, identify the user to speak came from a high accuracy can be achieved. Includes a speech signal pre-processing and voice feature extraction and voice emotion recognition.

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript.
- Framework: Vuejs, Libraries: jQuery.
- Office 365 apps: word, PowerPoint, Excel.
- Excellent IT and interpersonal communication skills.
- A creative and enthusiastic approach both in and out of the classroom.
- Good team member, able to work under pressure.
- · High work ethics.

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native.English: Good.